等待响应，点击该按钮运行程序。
Now for the moment you've been waiting for. Let's run the app by clicking on
它会提示我们选择设备。在没有物理设备时，
this button. It will prompt us to choose a device. Without a physical device we
我们可以使用 Android SDK 中的模拟器。
can use the emulator which is included in the Android SDK.
但是现在，还没有创建android虚拟设备。
Currently it says that there are no Android virtual devices available. So,
让我们打开AVD管理器来创建一个。点击新建。
let's open up the AVD manager to create one. Then click New. By creating an AVD,
创建AVD时，我们可以配置一个测试需要版本和硬件选项的模拟装置。
we can configure an emulated device with the android platform version that we
对于我们来说，
want to test on, as well as hardware options. For our case,
我们需要配置的虚拟设备Nexus 5，选项默认就ok了。
we're going to emulate a Nexus 5 virtual device, the defaults are fine for now.
点击ok，现在我们可以看见一个被成功创建的AVD。
So, we're going to hit OK. Then we see that our AVD was created successfully.
关闭AVD管理器。回到设备选择器对话框，
We can close the AVD Manager. And when we go back to the Device Chooser dialog,
可以看见有Nexus 5这个选项。点击OK,启动程序。
we'll see that Nexus5 is an option. Then we can hit OK to launch the app.
程序加载，我们可以看见Sunshine程序上显示的"Hello world"。
When it loads up, we see our Sunshine app with the words Hello world.
请记住，模拟器不仅仅是一个模拟器。
Keep in mind that the emulator is not just a simulator.
它是实际运行Android虚拟机。
It's actually running the Android Virtual Machine. So you can test and
所以你可以在不同的硬件和软件配置上测试和调试你的程序。
debug your app on different hardware and software configurations.
你可以在模拟器的屏幕上操控导航来与模拟器进行交互。
You can interact with the app on the emulator using the screen or
你也可以调用其他的应用程序，
with the navigation controls here. You can also invoke other apps,
比如网络电话、音乐播放器、视频播放器等。
do network calls, play audio or video and much more. It also includes debug
它还能够调试、输出日志，以及捕捉模拟应用程序和延迟网络的能力。
capabilities, including log output, and the ability to simulate app entraps or
你也可以返回主页，查看其他的应用程序。
network latency. You can also hit Home and browse around the device to see other
例如，你可以查看API demo。
apps. For example, you can check out API demos. Feel free to
自由的使用你的模拟器。当你打开Android设备检测器时，
play around with the emulator some more. If you open up Android Device Monitor,
你可以进入模拟器控制选项卡。
you can go into the Emulator Control Tab. There you'll see different options for
你将看见不同选项的模拟行为，例如电话和定位。
simulating behavior on your AVD, such as for telephony and for
现在，那句"Hello world"正在应用程序上执行着，
location. Now that the Hello world app runs on the emulator,
让我们看看这背后是如何让程序跑起来的吧！
let's see what goes on behind the scenes to make the app run.